<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- IBM_PROLOG_BEGIN_TAG                                                   -->
<!-- This is an automatically generated prolog.                             -->
<!--                                                                        -->
<!-- $Source: src/usr/diag/prdf/data/chip_data/p10/node_pau_phy_fir.xml $   -->
<!--                                                                        -->
<!-- OpenPOWER HostBoot Project                                             -->
<!--                                                                        -->
<!-- Contributors Listed Below - COPYRIGHT 2020                             -->
<!-- [+] International Business Machines Corp.                              -->
<!--                                                                        -->
<!--                                                                        -->
<!-- Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");        -->
<!-- you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.       -->
<!-- You may obtain a copy of the License at                                -->
<!--                                                                        -->
<!--     http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0                         -->
<!--                                                                        -->
<!-- Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software    -->
<!-- distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,      -->
<!-- WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or        -->
<!-- implied. See the License for the specific language governing           -->
<!-- permissions and limitations under the License.                         -->
<!--                                                                        -->
<!-- IBM_PROLOG_END_TAG                                                     -->
<attn_node model_ec="P10_10" name="PAU_PHY_FIR" reg_type="SCOM">
    <local_fir config="W" name="PAU_PHY_FIR">
        <instance addr="0x10012C00" reg_inst="0"/>
        <instance addr="0x11012C00" reg_inst="1"/>
        <instance addr="0x12012C00" reg_inst="2"/>
        <instance addr="0x13012C00" reg_inst="3"/>
        <action attn_type="CS" config="00"/>
        <action attn_type="RE" config="01"/>
        <action attn_type="SPA" config="10"/>
        <action attn_type="UCS" config="11"/>
    </local_fir>
    <bit pos="0">FIR Register - A RX state machine parity or mode register parity error has occurred (IOO0).</bit>
    <bit pos="1">FIR Register - A RX state machine parity or mode register parity error has occurred (IOO1).</bit>
    <bit pos="2">FIR Register - A RX state machine parity or mode register parity error has occurred (OMI0).</bit>
    <bit pos="3">FIR Register - A RX state machine parity or mode register parity error has occurred (OMI1).</bit>
    <bit pos="4">FIR Register - A TX state machine parity or mode register parity error has occurred (IOO0).</bit>
    <bit pos="5">FIR Register - A TX state machine parity or mode register parity error has occurred (IOO1).</bit>
    <bit pos="6">FIR Register - A TX state machine parity or mode register parity error has occurred (OMI0).</bit>
    <bit pos="7">FIR Register - A TX state machine parity or mode register parity error has occurred (OMI1).</bit>
    <bit pos="8">FIR Register - A TX ZCAL state machine parity or mode register parity error has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="9">FIR Register - A PPE internal error has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="10">FIR Register - A PPE external error has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="11">FIR Register - A PPE Halt due to Watchdog or Interrupt has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="12">FIR Register - A PPE Halt due to Debug has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="13">FIR Register - PPE Halted.</bit>
    <bit pos="14">FIR Register - A PPE Watchdog Timeout has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="15">FIR Register - A PPE Array Scrub was missed.</bit>
    <bit pos="16">FIR Register - A PPE Array uncorrectable error has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="17">FIR Register - A PPE Array correctable error has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="18">FIR Register - A PPE Code Recal Abort has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="19">FIR Register - A PPE Code Fatal Error has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="20">FIR Register - A PPE Code Warning has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="21">FIR Register - A PPE Code DFT Error has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="22">FIR Register - A PPE Code Recal Not Run has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="23">FIR Register - A PPE Code Thread Locked has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="24">FIR Register - A PPE Code FIR 6 has occurred.</bit>
    <bit pos="25">FIR Register - A PPE Code FIR 7 has occurred.</bit>
</attn_node>
